{
    "id": "fe8edd7ab868480f8bd30f6592a78c4d",
    "title": "Perfect Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have not visited this town .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9482661a3841483fb02af4bafb4a01bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................................... with us for over five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "was working",
                "has been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "02378e7035744bcfbbc795fd20288352"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ............................................ each other for two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been knowing",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "86c889d2f02d466dad010bcd820aecc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have not been on friendly terms ...................................... nearly two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8343f4e6e8fe4bf582fe46556a859d55"
        },
        {
            "question": "What have you been doing .................................. 10 oâ€™clock this morning?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1761632df314c7485b45d85ef4edf2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ to my native place since last January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am not",
                "have not been",
                "had not gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db76cc1f83764c068bc266e371dd431b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has not paid his monthly subscription ........................................ a year now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a484c97c09b40168c3eb6458604de7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ....................................... in touch with each other for one year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "102ba0dbbc2c4f43a3a51f4371b66217"
        },
        {
            "question": "His son has been undergoing treatment ........................................ two months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26e83c4b34fd4caaa12315b896dca48a"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... when have you been learning music?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5111b8d3220c471c9f6d0645c2bc6c7d"
        }
    ]
}